H.R. Johnson

Freelancer in Kalamazoo, Michigan 360-951-0354 find.serendipity@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/findserendipity

Summary

Outgoing, resilient professional with background in full-stack development, community management and white-glove customer service. Experienced with cold and warm sales calls, meeting quotas and KPIs, and collaborating with cross-functional teams to drive customer-centric solutions.

Skills

Tools & Technologies || Google Suite, Google Apps Scripts, Figma, Miro, Jira, Confluence, HubSpot CRM, Zendesk, GitHub, Kanban, Agile

Proficiencies | Sales, Luxury Customer Service, Content Creation, Community Management

Experience

Communitrix, Remote | Founder

August 2023 - Current

- Obtained and maintained small but strong client base
- Drafted and implemented custom community plans for clients
- Maintained client codebases and updated websites with modern security
- Created standard and milestone-based contracts for clients

Community.co, Remote | Community Manager

July 2019 - June 2023

- Upsold events and memberships to members via forums and email marketing campaigns
- Managed communities for various high-profile clients, increasing community engagement from 2% to 7%
- Designed and developed Google Apps Scripts for engagement and retention projects
- Trained team members in data collection, analysis, and reporting

Internet Brands, Remote | Community Manager

July 2013 - July 2019

- Created incentives for members to purchase larger or longer memberships
- Managed cross-functional teams in community forums and customer support
- Increased customer satisfaction from 61% to 96% through strategic initiatives
- Handled customer support issues and abuse reports

Education

Fullstack Academy, Remote \parallel Student

Feb 2024 - June 2024

- Top-ranking graduate of the online full-time full-stack web development bootcamp
- \bullet Conducted user research and implemented design changes to enhance user's experience
- Gained expertise in modern user design principals and front-end development
- Managed projects using Agile methodologies, focusing on user-centered design

University of Washington, Seattle, WA

2011

Bachelor of Arts in Anthropology & Archaeology, Summa cum laude